const STORE = [
    {
      question: 'What type of plant is used to make tequila?',
      answers: [
        'Aloe',
        'Sugar cane',
        'Agave',
        'Corn'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'answer-three'
    },
  
    {
      question: 'Where does tequila get its name?',
      answers: [
        'The town called Tequila, where much of the liquor is produced.',
        'Eduardo Tequila, the first person to mass produce the spirit.',
        'The aztec deity Tequila who was associated with the agave plant.',
        'The San Antonio tavern Tequila that first popularized the beverage.'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'answer-one'
    },
  
    {
      question: 'On average, how many years does it take for an agave plant to reach maturity for harvest?',
      answers: [
        '2-3',
        '4-6',
        '8-10',
        '15-20'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'answer-three'
    },
  
    {
      question: `Which of the following matches these categories of tequila:<br>Aged 1-2 months / Aged 2 - 12 months / Aged 1 - 3 years`,
      answers: [
        'Joven / mediano / viejo',
        'Silver / bronze / gold',
        'Reposado / anejo / muy anejo',
        'Blanco / reposado / anejo'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'answer-four'
    },
  
    {
      question: `Put these events in the correct order of tequila production:<br>
      A: The agave is shredded and the juice is extracted.<br>
      B: The liquid, called mosto, is distilled.<br>
      C: The agave is cooked to convert complex sugars to simple sugars.<br>
      D: The juice is fermented, converting sugar into alcohol.`,
      answers: [
        'A - C - D - B',
        'C - A - D - B',
        'C - A - B - D',
        'A - D - C - B'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'answer-two'
    },
  
    {
      question: 'Which of the following is NOT a key difference between tequila and mezcal?',
      answers: [
        'Tequila is made from the whole, roasted agaves, while mezcal uses the sugary sap from the plant.',
        'Tequila must be made from Blue Agave while mezcal can be made from many different types of agave.',
        'Tequila primarily comes from the Mexican state of Jalisco, while mezcal production is centered in Oaxaca.',
        'For tequila, the agave is baked in ovens. For mezcal it is roasted in earthen pits, often lending a smokey flavor.'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'answer-one'
    },
  
    {
      question: 'Which of the following is NOT a spirit made from agave?',
      answers: [
        'Cachaca',
        'Raicilla',
        'Mezcal',
        'Bacanora'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'answer-one'
    },
  
    {
      question: 'Which of these statements is true?',
      answers: [
        'Mezcal is a specific type of Tequila.',
        'Mezcal and Tequila are the same thing.',
        'Tequila is a specific type of Mezcal.',
        'Mezcal and Tequila are completely separate spirits.'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'answer-three'
    },
  
    {
      question: 'What is the fermented beverage made from agave sap (aguamiel) called?',
      answers: [
        'Sotol',
        'Ordinario',
        'Mosto',
        'Pulque'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'answer-four'
    },
  
    {
      question: 'Which of the following is NOT true of the quiote, the tall flowering stalk that grows from the agave plant?',
      answers: [
        'It is commonly cut down to prevent sugars being diverted away from the agave pina.',
        'It is how the agave plant sexually reproduces and its flowers are fertilized by bats and hummingbirds.',
        'It can be cooked and eaten, or dried and used similarly to wooden posts.',
        'It is cut down and used to make a special type of mezcal.'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'answer-four'
    }
  ];